outletgo.net 2013-06-08

# Privacy Policy | OutletGo.net

We consider your privacy a high priority. We are fully committed to respecting your privacy and to protecting any personal data you provide to us. 

This statement comprises the privacy policy of our web site **OutletGo.net** and explains how we collect, use, transfer, store and disclose your personal information.

**OutletGo.net** reviews and updates this policy periodically, as needed, without notice. Therefore, we advise you to review the terms of this policy systematically. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by **OutletGo.net** as explained below.

## Personal Information

"Personal Information" is the information that identifies you as an individual, such as name, postal address, telephone number, email address and credit or debit card number.

You can visit our website without explicitly providing any personal information. 

We may collect your personal identifiable information only when you choose to submit it to us. 

In addition, as with many other web servers, we may also collect and log tracking information via website request data and response data. This policy applies to all information (User Information) gathered by the Website.

## Use of Personal Information

**OutletGo.net** is fully committed to the privacy of the User Information collected by our web site and will not share any personal information to any third parties. We use your Registration Information, specifically your phone number or email address, primarily to contact you regarding new products, offers, surveys, requests, notices and other information relevant to your use of our website.

Our company will use your Payment Information only to make payment transactions required to conduct business and complete buying or selling operations. Your payment information may be shared with banks and credit card agencies. It may also be used to check your credit-worthiness. 

**OutletGo.net** uses up-to-date technology and internal procedures to guard your Payment Information against intruders. Even so, there is no guarantee that such technology or procedure can eliminate all of the risks of theft, loss or misuse of this data. Our company shall not be liable to you or any other person for any damages that might result from unauthorized use, publication, disclosure or any other misuse of Payment Information, including credit card information.

## Disclosure of Information

We only share your Personal Information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose the data you provide on **OutletGo.net** to relevant authorities in case we find it necessary to identify, contact and bring legal action against persons who infringe or intend to infringe or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of OutletGo.net, our Users, customers, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

If we have a reason to believe that a User is in breach with the Terms and Conditions published on **OutletGo.net** , we reserve the right to disclose his information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to the site or others. 

## Cookies

Like most websites, **OutletGo.net** uses cookies to store your profile. A cookie is a small text file placed on the user's hard drive containing information about the User and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. Logging in our web site using cookies is in no way linked to any personal private data. Once the member closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates. Cookies make the interaction between users and web sites faster and easier. Without cookies, it would be very difficult for a website to allow a visitor to fill up a shopping cart or to remember the user's preferences or registration details for a future visit. 

## Security Measures 

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. 

While, our company takes all reasonable precautions to safeguard the privacy of your data, security risks cannot be completely eliminated and we therefore cannot guaranty total security.

## Changes to Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to modify this **Privacy Policy** from time to time, without prior notification to our Users. When we post changes to the **Privacy Policy** , we will revise the "last modified" date at the top of this page. We encourage our members to periodically review our **Privacy Policy** to be informed of how **OutletGo.net** protects your data.

## External Links

Our website may contain links to websites and other information created and maintained by other individuals and organizations. Such external websites have their own privacy policies separate from this policy. Even if the third party is affiliated with **OutletGo.net** through a business partnership or otherwise, **OutletGo.net** is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of such external links. We do not control or guarantee the correctness, timeliness, completeness, or relevance of any information or privacy policies posted on these linked websites. These links are only provided for your convenience and you access them at your own risk. You are encouraged to report links that are non-functional or a linked site that you feel contains material that is not appropriate for a general website viewing audience.

## Terms of Use

Violation of the terms of use set forth in our policy may result in suspension or termination of web site account access. Our company reserves the right to suspend web site account access without warning if we have reason to believe these terms of use have been violated.

## Your Feedback

**OutletGo.net** welcomes your suggestions, remarks, questions and any other correspondence related to your use of our website. Please contact us at **OutletGo.net**.
